CHANEL PEASE

U/X U/I DESIGNER MUSIC ENGINEER

EXPERIENCES

Growit App

DESIGNER / PROJECT MANAGER

2016

Growit is a social app that brings the gardening community together within geographic regions. App features include sharing photos, plant information, explore and search

Accomplishments

- Led a team of developers to conceptualize, design and develop a new feature on the app to solve a problem with the user experience
- The feature combined interactive communication with it's users as a chat and Q & A.

MUSICAL ARTIST ENGINEER

2014-2015

Composed, performed, recorded, and engineered music for several albums, commercials and films.

Accomplishments

- FILM: Burnt in Memory FILM SCORE COMPOSER & RECORDING ARTIST: Harp, Organ CO-COMPOSER &
- ARTIST: Via Tania ALBUM:Tomorrow Music Orchestra • ARTIST: Pulseprogramming RECORDING ARTIST: Harp
- ALBUM: Then It All Came Down CO-COMPOSER, ENGINEER RECORDING ARTIST: Voice, Kevboards
- ARTIST: Wrekmeister Harmonies ALBUM: You've Always Meant So • ARTIST: Lindsay Anderson Much To Me RECORDING ARTIST: Harp
- COMMERCIAL : Johnnie Walker Black Label **RECORDING ARTIST**
- ALBUM: Charade is Gold Voice, Keyboards
 - ARTIST: Costa Music ALBUM: Lighter Subjects WRITER, RECORDING
 - ARTIST: Voice, Keyboards

ALBUM: If

RECORDING ARTIST: Harp

HOSPITALITY GENERAL MANAGER 1999-2014

As General Manager, oversaw all management of personnel, implemented staff training and education, streamlined operations management and work-flow, developed marketing campaigns, oversaw vendor relations and inventory management, and programmed all Point of Sale software.

Accomplishments

- The Charleston/General Manager:
 - Developed marketing and re-branding campaign resulting in over 300% new revenue.
- Terry Alexander (One Off Hospitality)/General Manager: Held various GM and management positions for Terry Alexander including The Violet Hour, Del Toro, Mod, Francesca's Forno, Danny's Tavern and MOD.
- Beverly Wilshire Hotel, Beverly Hills / Special Event Coordinator, Food & Beverage Manager: Held various management positions, managed guest relations of celebrities and royalty.

PROFILE

Multi-media artist specializing in UX UI Design and music composition, engineering and sound design. Composed and recorded music for commercials, fullfeature films, and video shorts. Extensive experience in restaurant technologies; programming remote/digital point of sale systems, menu design/layout, and promotional graphics. 15+ years in the hospitality industry in management positions as a team leader, staff trainer, and helped produce a service driven environment.

EDUCATION

STARTUP INSTITUTE CHICAGO

Web Design Track

- The Startup Institute Web Design Track is a highly selective and immersive program designed to cover every phase of front-end development and interface design with an emphasis on usercentered principles.
- Built on the product development life cycle, the curriculum simulates real-life challenges to prepare designers to successfully take a project from concept to launch.
- The Design program intensely covers universal principals of U/X and U/I Design.
- The industry languages HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and jQuery are learned at a highly functional and comprehensive level.

BYU IDAHO

2015-present

Software Engineering Program

VOLUNTEER

Foundations in Music (Rock for Kids)/Volunteer 2010-2011 Taught children music in three different Chicago Public Schools, in various foster homes and Catholic Charities after school programs.

T2 (AIDS Foundation of Chicago) 2009-2010: Trained with the team and raised \$1500 towards the charity, volunteered at the training events and the following year for The Chicago Marathon.

EXPERTISE

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- ¡Query
- Pro-Tools
- Fonts and layouts
- High fidelity mockups
- Rapid prototyping
- Navigation flow
- Music composition
- Project management
 Sound engineering

LinkedIn Github

Tel. 312 608 8707 Web. www.chanelpease.com chanelelisa@gmail.com Email.